Over these past three days,
I've learned a lot about you, Hioki.
And it's made me want to
get to know you even better.
So...
If you don't mind, will you...
No way...
Is he about to confess his feelings for me?
Will you...
be my friend?
Huh?
Fr-friends?
Yeah.
Friends.
Huh...?
Sorry.
Huh?
Oh, no, what I meant was...
I guess I already
thought of you as a friend.
So... sorry about that.
Oh...
So, um...
I'm really happy.
I'm happy you said that.
I'd like that, too. I'm
looking forward to it.
Thank you.
But...
When I say "friend"...
I don't mean just a regular friend.
Huh?
What do you mean by that?
Uh... well... for example...
When you're feeling lonely, Hioki...
I want you to call me without hesitating.
And when you're having a tough time, too.
I want to be the first, the first person...
the first person you think to turn to.
Oh...
So, in other words,
a relationship where we
don't have to hold back? Right...?
Thank you.
Then that's what I'll do.
Okay.
Then we'll do that.
Ah.
Well then...
I'm looking forward to it.
Me too.
Yeah.
"School Trip: Joined a Group I'm Not Close to"
- Good morning.
- Morning.
(Episode 5: School Assembly)
So cute.
Three months had passed
since the start of the second year.
Hioki.
Morning.
- Morning.
In my class,
I made some new friends.
Do you have a charger...
Yeah.
Making friends...
is something I should be grateful for...
Hioki.
I'll help you.
- No... but...
- We're friends, right?
Thank you.
For someone like me,
who's used to being alone,
it still isn't familiar.
Hioki.
- Let's go.
- Oh, sorry, sorry.
Passing from behind is dangerous!
Hehehe...
Hioki, hold on.
Oh, huh? Oh, sorry.
Omgggggg look.
- Wow, so cool.
- Like a prince.
There you go.
Oh... thank you.
I'm not used to it.
Hioki, do you like sausages?
- Yeah.
- I brought extra.
- Here, have one.
- Oh... thanks.
Thank you.
I'm not used to it...
but really, friends do all this for each other?
Well then... Hioki.
Want my konjac?
Huh?
You can have my broccoli, too.
You guys just don't like
it yourselves, do you?
Then... here you go.
- Don't just put it in there!
- Hold on.
No, no, no.
Oh, want some?
Here.
Mm.
Sweet.
Thanks.
I have no idea what the
definition of a "friend" is anymore.
Hey, the bell rang. Let's pack up.
Next is the school-wide assembly.
We'll be reviewing the field trip.
So don't forget your
handbooks and writing utensils.
Okay.
- Don't forget, everyone.
- Okay!
Hayato, could you please erase the board?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Hioki.
Let's go together.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Come on, let's go.
Alright, please line up with your classes.
Class 5 is over here!
Okay, next up...
we're going to play a video of some
of the highlights from the field trip.
Oh! If you can't see the
screen well, feel free to move.
Hioki.
What should we do? Should we move too?
Huh?
The back...
Let's watch from the back.
Sure.
Let's do it then. Come on, come on.
- Let's go.
- Hey, wait.
Oh, sorry, I can walk on my own.
Watarai.
Here, this is... for you.
Sorry.
It's fine. Stay like that.
Alright then...
It's starting.
(Kazamino High School
School Trip Memories)
Ooh.
Here it comes.
The teacher's so cute!
Aren't we...
a little too close?
Or rather,
right now am I using the most
handsome guy at school as back support?
- Hey, that's us.
- That's right.
Ugh, wait, I look so bad.
This is awful. What's with that face?
Give me a break.
Since we're friends,
this should be okay, right?
But...
if Watarai's fans saw us like this...
I can't see if you
keep fidgeting like that.
If this keeps up, my life will...
What do you mean?
Oh no!
What are you doing?
There.
Those who have handed in their handbooks
can return to the classroom for self-study.
Oh, the reflection section...
You need to fill out at least 80% of it.
A reflection, huh?
Oh, are you writing something?
No, not yet.
I see.
Um...
Oh, Tsujitani!
Sorry, I'm borrowing Hioki for a sec.
Can you please stop staring at people?
He got borrowed.
Tsujitani...
- You were in a group with the Four Heavenly Kings...
- What's with that reaction?
I can't even deal with it anymore.
I'm so bummed out...
Seriously.
By the way, who was that just now?
Tsujitani. He went to my junior high.
And those guys over there,
I think they're all on the badminton team.
Huh?
Hioki's on the badminton team?
Oh, yeah.
Wait, he's in a sports club?
That's pretty surprising.
It is.
Right, Watarai?
Oh, yeah.
I've been playing since junior high.
Whoa, you can play?
What the hell?
- That was so nerve-wracking.
- What?
What's wrong?
It's not what's wrong with us.
It's you.
Please stop hanging out in a
place that's so hard to approach.
Wow.
Ahh...
That's true.
It does take a bit of
courage to go over there.
More than a bit...
Look, my hands are still shaking.
Is it that bad?
I mean, if you're that nervous,
then we should all go
together for moral support.
No, no, no, no, no!
Don't be ridiculous.
The three of us...
Combined...
our power level...
is only around 30.
Yeah.
Even if you add Hioki,
our power level is only 20.
- How did it go down?!
- Huh...
- Don't "huh" me.
Anyway, forget that. What's up?
- Why'd you call me here?
- About the club...
Oh, right, right, right, right. That's it.
No, I mean...
it's about passing out the club souvenirs.
- I wanted to figure out who's doing what.
- I see.
By the way,
you've gotten really close to them.
The Four Heavenly Kings.
Yeah, I guess.
- I guess you could call us friends...
- Friends?
- Seriously?
- I think so...
- Friends?
You...
You've totally become
one of the popular kids.
I'm so jealous, you wannabe cool kid.
Whoa, that's a little harsh.
Alright, okay, it's done.
What do you think?
Hey.
Watarai, are you done writing?
Watarai.
Are you okay?
- Are you okay?
- Hey.
You okay?
- Sorry.
- What took you so long?
Sorry.
Huh?
Oh, I handed in your
notebook already, is that OK?
Oh, sorry. Thanks.
- No problem.
- Thank you.
- Sorry to keep you waiting.
- Thanks.
Oh, and also,
the teacher asked me
to help lock up and clean.
Hioki, can you check the second floor?
Let's split up.
- Got it.
- Yeah, thanks.
- I'm heading up.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Come on, you come too. - No, no.
- Why not?
Hioki.
I'll go with you.
What were you guys
talking about just now?
Huh?
With your club friends.
Oh, nothing important.
Just about the club souvenirs.
Why do you ask?
It's nothing.
Watarai.
What's up with you?
Nothing.
I was just a little curious.
You just looked like you were having fun.
What's that supposed to mean?
Don't tell me you're jealous.
Yeah.
Huh?
- Did you really write that?
- The guy is full of it.
- I just thought it was funny.
- I could never write that.
Being jealous of your friends.
Is that wrong?
It's not that it's wrong...
No.
Am I wrong?
For me,
actually...
Hioki, Hioki, Hioki!
Look, a new racket.
You bought another one?
You're such a gearhead.
Hey, don't knock it.
I'm telling you, this thing is light.
Before we became friends,
I was always...
I was always so impatient
about the distance between us.
Watarai? Are you okay?
Huh?
Why are you hugging me all of a sudden?
- Just for a little bit...
- Huh?
Because I'm lonely.
Let me stay like this
for just a little longer.
What?
This...
feeling...
Ah...
Um...
Watarai.
Hioki.
Where are they?
Then again, it's not like
you were really looking.
I was...
Come on... You're so unreliable.
Hey...
Do friends...
do this kind of stuff?
I would.
Is that wrong?
It's not that it's wrong,
but... isn't that a little long for a hug?
Only with Hioki...
You...
- What about kissing a friend?
- Wait... what?
Well...
that kind of thing...
you can't do that.
That kind of...
That...
What's gotten into you all of a sudden?
It's nothing.
I won't do it. Yet.
Yet...?
What do you mean by that?
But I've said it now.
Huh?
That we're not just friends.
Hey, there he is.
Hey, what are you two doing?
Sorry, I'll be right there.
I'm going ahead.
Okay, I'll leave the rest to you.
What the...
is going on?
That just now...
What took you so long?
Sorry.
What were you guys doing?
It's a secret.
Hey.
What? What is it?
Now I'm curious.
It was nothing.
Hioki just got tangled up in some cords.
It just took a minute to sort out.
Oh, so it was just a little accident.
Anyway, are we going anywhere after school?
It's so hot. I'm craving some ice cream.
Oh, should we go to a
family restaurant then?
And make some plans?
Plans for summer break.
- Yeah, sounds good. - Yeah, yeah.
- Summer break.
- The beach, the beach!
- The beach!
Before that,
we still have finals.
I don't get it.
I don't get what Watarai is thinking.
Summer break is coming.
Let's just forget about it for now.
Let's go then...
- Let's go, let's go, let's go!
- Let's go study.
- Let's go, the beach is waiting for me.
- My beach is waiting.
We're friends,
but I don't understand him at all.
Hioki.
- Oh, let's hurry.
- Sorry, sorry.
Four months into my sophomore year,
still riding the high from the school trip
and exhausted from final exams,
our long-awaited
summer break had finally arrived.
Anyway, today's plan was to
go to the beach with everyone.
But...
of all things, I was the
only one running late.
Are you Hioki Asahi?
Hey~
You're pretty cute.
Who are you?
(Next Episode Preview)
Here we go, the ocean!
(A Summer Break with the Hottest Guys)
What happens to the loser? Let's start with a penalty game.
Huh?
Whoa!
(So Hot, Our Love is Heating Up Fast?)
Huh?
- The ice is melting...
- Ah.
Well then I'll go ahead.